<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Peter Le</title>
    <link>https://peterle.github.io/Peter_Porfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Peter Le</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://peterle.github.io/Peter_Porfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Things to know before planning a trip to Toronto</title>
      <link>https://peterle.github.io/Peter_Porfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterle.github.io/Peter_Porfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Toronto Airbnb Dataset Analysis
The Motivation for the Project
This project (Write a Data Science Blog Post) is part of Udacity Data Scientist Nanodegree Program. I used Toronto Airbnb Dataset for this project as its the city I live in. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in using data science techniques to analyze ways to improve future listings. The questions analyzed may be similar to data sources one might encounter in a business setting. Additionally, many of the approaches and skills used in this project can be applicable to future work projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Battle of Neighborhoods</title>
      <link>https://peterle.github.io/Peter_Porfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterle.github.io/Peter_Porfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Overview
The purpose of this project is to assist people in researching the most optimal and resourceful locations near their neighborhood. It will provide the necessary information in making the best decision on selecting the neighborhood you would like to live in.
Many people move into parts of Canada and need tons of prior research dealing with factors such as suitable housing prices, well-known schools for their children, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter V: Quasimodo</title>
      <link>https://peterle.github.io/Peter_Porfolio/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterle.github.io/Peter_Porfolio/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>In the twinkling of an eye, all was ready to execute Coppenole’s idea. Bourgeois, scholars and law clerks all set to work. The little chapel situated opposite the marble table was selected for the scene of the grinning match. A pane broken in the pretty rose window above the door, left free a circle of stone through which it was agreed that the competitors should thrust their heads. In order to reach it, it was only necessary to mount upon a couple of hogsheads, which had been produced from I know not where, and perched one upon the other, after a fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>https://peterle.github.io/Peter_Porfolio/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterle.github.io/Peter_Porfolio/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III: Monsieur the Cardinal</title>
      <link>https://peterle.github.io/Peter_Porfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peterle.github.io/Peter_Porfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Poor Gringoire! the din of all the great double petards of the Saint-Jean, the discharge of twenty arquebuses on supports, the detonation of that famous serpentine of the Tower of Billy, which, during the siege of Paris, on Sunday, the twenty-sixth of September, 1465, killed seven Burgundians at one blow, the explosion of all the powder stored at the gate of the Temple, would have rent his ears less rudely at that solemn and dramatic moment, than these few words, which fell from the lips of the usher, “His eminence, Monseigneur the Cardinal de Bourbon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
